

jessicajzhong@gmail.com

650-255-2187



linkedin.com/in/jessicazhong



jessicazhong.design

SUMMARY

A UX/UI Designer with a business acumen focused on people. I am committed to creating better user-focused experiences through a deep understanding of people by identifying real-life problems and crafting thoughtful solutions grounded by research

EDUCATION

BLOC.IO

UX/UI Design Apprenticeship Nov 2018 - June 2019

UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA **SAN DIEGO**

B.S Management Science

SKILLS

DESIGN

UX Design Visual Design **User Research Usability Testing Brand Design & Identity** Information Architecture Wireframing **Prototyping** Sketching

DESIGN TOOLS

Sketch

Figma

UsabilityHub

InVision

Affinity Designer

Draw.io

Maze

WEB DEVELOPMENT

HTML5

CSS3

JavaScript (basic)

RECENT PROJECTS

TRAVELPAK | WEB & MOBILE APPLICATION

jessicazhong.design/project2.html

- A travel planning web and mobile application designed to help group travelers plan, manage and organize trips, making group travel planning easier than ever
- Utilized Sketch, InVision, lofi wireframes, hi-mockups, in-person usability testing, visual and interation design with branding and content development

HEALTHPOINT | MOBILE APPLICATION

jessicazhong.design/project1.html

- A cloud-based mobile application that provides health enthusiasts an improved way to collect and store data, with the ability to analyze, connect and organize in the palm of their hand
- Utilized Sketch, Figma, Draw.io to create user flows, wireframes, mockups, usability testing and branding work

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE | UX/UI DESIGNER

June 2019 - current

- Providing UX consultation and visual designs for client's communication mobile application, securing \$500K of initial funding
- Web presence and responsive design for a rebranding of e-commerce boutique
- Strategizing and collaborating with clients by producing lofi wireframes, sitemap, and hi-fi mockups
- Developing brand design, visual design and style guide

JOBVITE | HR GENERALIST

Apr 2017 - Jan 2019

- Spearheaded company's first Wellness Initiative, resulting in a 45% participation rate for the first year, across all programs for a company of 195 employees
- Implemented a candidate-focused and new hire survey into Jobvite's platform to analyze tangible data regarding the health of Jobvite's brand and candidate experience